<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Blog Name</title>
  <subtitle>Blog subtitle</subtitle>
  <id>http://blog.url.com/</id>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/"/>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2021-07-09T20:00:00-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Blog Author</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>A Better Clojure Job Board</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/2021/07/10/a-better-clojure-job-board.html"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/2021/07/10/a-better-clojure-job-board.html</id>
    <published>2021-07-09T20:00:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-07-11T10:57:11-04:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I've rebuilt &lt;a href="https://jobs.braveclojure.com/"&gt;Brave Clojure Jobs&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;strong&gt;make it
effortless to advertise Clojure jobs.&lt;/strong&gt; If you're hiring, I want you to be able
to get a job listing in front of interested devs in less time than it takes you
to sing Queen's &lt;em&gt;We Are the Champions&lt;/em&gt;. Watch how quick and easy it is to sign
up and post a listing:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width="750" height="422" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xLhBCCnLegM" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen="" style="display: block; margin: 0 auto"&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here's what's new:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s now freemium.&lt;/strong&gt; You can post as many listings as you want without
giving a credit card number. Charging per listing is nice for the job board's
owner (me!), but I don't think it's the best model if the job board is to be
as &lt;em&gt;useful&lt;/em&gt; as possible. The most useful job board would include every
available opening, so I've tried to remove barriers to that goal. At the same
time, I do want to make money with this endeavor; I'll describe the paid
benefits below.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You can import listings.&lt;/strong&gt; If you manage listings with Greenhouse, Workable,
and similar services you can just paste a listing's URL to import it.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You can duplicate listings.&lt;/strong&gt; You can now create new listings from existing
listings. The theme here is: make it super easy to create listings!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Copy/paste preserves formatting.&lt;/strong&gt; If you copy a listing you've created
elsewhere and paste it in Brave Clojure Jobs, it will preserve the formatting,
automatically converting it to markdown. I hope you'll find that this kind of
attention to detail makes using Brave Clojure Jobs a great experience :D&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Companies are first-class.&lt;/strong&gt; You can now create a company profile. Your
profile page will include links to all your listings, and it will appear in
the site's company directory.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I've filled out your company profile for you.&lt;/strong&gt; I have been creating
profiles for dozens of companies looking for Clojure developers. Be on the
lookout for a link from me which will allow you to easily create a Brave
Clojure Jobs user account associated with your company. The video shows how
this works. I really want to make it easy for you to connect with a large
audience of Clojure developers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you go through the process of "sign up with pre-filled company profile then
import listing" you could have a listing published in a minute or less.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Removing barriers to posting listings results in more listings.&lt;/strong&gt; This makes Brave
Clojure Jobs more valuable to developers, growing the site's audience, which in
turn makes it more valuable to companies. It's a virtuous cycle. (Side note: I'm
really patting myself on the back for using the term "virtuous cycle.")&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also want to definitively show that &lt;strong&gt;companies are hiring Clojure
developers&lt;/strong&gt;, now more than ever. In this way, I hope the site benefits the
Clojure community as a whole by correcting the perception that not many places
hire Clojure devs. I still see people ask, "Can I get paid to write Clojure?"
It's a concern for anyone considering learning the language; it's a large time
investment and people naturally want it to pay off. I want to show that &lt;strong&gt;the
payoff is real&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Indeed, I've seen a considerable uptick in Clojure job postings in 2021. More
and more companies want to hire people to write Clojure because they know doing
so brings tangible benefits. This site will be the beautifully-designed proof.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, a secondary goal of this rewrite is to create a marketing tool for the
community: I want something we can point to to show that &lt;strong&gt;if you learn Clojure
won't just become a better programmer, you'll also gain access to expanded
career opportunities&lt;/strong&gt;. This will help grow the community, which in turn will
help us &lt;span style="text-decoration: line-through"&gt;take over the programming
world&lt;/span&gt; make the language an even more viable choice for everybody.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many more changes – the UI is leagues better, there's better
integration with Stripe so you can manage payments without having to contact me,
etc. etc. etc. The main point is that I want the site help us all as much as a
job board possibly can. My hope is that this massive upgrade, which I've worked
on for over a year, will be good for companies, good for developers, and good
for the entire Clojure community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="subscription-benefits"&gt;Subscription benefits&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are three subscription levels available to companies: $75/month,
$150/month, and $250/month. Paying for a subscription gives you greater
exposure: paying companies are listed on the home page as "supporters", and
their listings are highlighted and placed higher. Subscribing companies will
also have their jobs tweeted and sent to the Brave Clojure Jobs mailing list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over time I want to continue increasing supporters' reach by placing listings in
more channels. For example, on the &lt;a href="https://trello.com/b/KLvxGv7u/product-roadmap"&gt;public product
roadmap&lt;/a&gt;, one of the first items
is "post bi-weekly job roundup to reddit.", and it's just one idea for how I
want to provide value for subscribers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another idea is to include badges or some kind of flair for subscribing
companies to help your company stand out. For example, I want to create a
"conference sponsor" badge. Conference sponsors deserve public recognition, and
I think highlighting such contributions is valuable for job seekers, as it's
more appealing to work for companies that we know are giving back to the
community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have ideas for what you'd like included in a paid subscription, please
let me know! You can reach me by email,
&lt;a href="&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#100;&amp;#097;&amp;#110;&amp;#105;&amp;#101;&amp;#108;&amp;#064;&amp;#098;&amp;#114;&amp;#097;&amp;#118;&amp;#101;&amp;#099;&amp;#108;&amp;#111;&amp;#106;&amp;#117;&amp;#114;&amp;#101;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;"&gt;&amp;#100;&amp;#097;&amp;#110;&amp;#105;&amp;#101;&amp;#108;&amp;#064;&amp;#098;&amp;#114;&amp;#097;&amp;#118;&amp;#101;&amp;#099;&amp;#108;&amp;#111;&amp;#106;&amp;#117;&amp;#114;&amp;#101;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&lt;/a&gt;. You can also upvote
items on the &lt;a href="https://trello.com/b/KLvxGv7u/product-roadmap"&gt;product roadmap&lt;/a&gt; if
they strike your fancy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The takeaway here is that there are currently some subscription benefits focused
on increasing your listings' reach, and there are some in the works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id="supporting-brave-clojure-jobs"&gt;Supporting Brave Clojure Jobs&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the same time, I have to be honest that I'm uncertain about the ROI for
subscribing. I believe that the subscription benefits will provide real value,
but right now I don't have the data to create a precisely compelling sales pitch
for just how much better you'll do if you subscribe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, I wanted to rebuild the site because I value generosity. Engaging
with others from a spirit of generosity just feels better to me. I wanted to
invest the effort to make improvements and switch to a freemium model because I
believe it will help everybody.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I may end up making less than before, who knows, but I wanted to try to
contribute more to a community that has been so good to me. I think I've
accomplished that. I also want to keep improving the site, and paid
subscriptions help me do that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My goal is to reach $2,000 a month in subscriptions. That level of support would
would be huge for me, and it would make it viable for me to continue investing a
significant portion of my free time in the site on an ongoing basis. If you
believe that this is a worthwhile endeavor and that it will help everybody in
the long run, including you, then I hope you'll subscribe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;– Daniel Higginbotham&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
